BM | BRADLEY MEYER |

(513) 578-0654

Brad.meyer13@gmail.com

8858 Cox Road, West Chester, OH 45069

PROFILE

"Two road diverged in a wood, and I took the one less traveled by" - Robert Frost. Buisness Professional with 3 years of Experience in the Real Estate Industry, very goal driven and a big picture thinker. My Biggest strengths are Buisness Awareness and communication, which enables me to permanently streamline work and inter-office worker relations. I hold myself to a high standard, I constantly push myself and those around me to be better each and every day.

EXPERIENCE

Firehouse Subs, West Chester, OH -2014-2019

Line worker, Shift Leader, & Management Training. 5 Years in the food service industry. Job duties included Customer service in food preparation and follow up (Refill, Communication, Clean up), Training, Assembly teamwork, Stock counting, basic skills (Dish clean up and trash removal). 2x Employee of the year

Marketing Assistant, Priority National Title, West Chester, OH — 2019-2020

Assistant to leading Marketer in Company. Job duties included, Client followup, Computer input, Information tracking, Client Gift ideas and preparation, Driving to offices to connect with clients and network, Client retention. 2019 Marketing MVP (Assistant)

Realtor, Coldwell Banker Realty, West Chester, OH — 2020-2021

Team member. Job duties included, Helping people through the stressful home buying process, driving out to show homes and host open-houses, attend marketing and Buisness event to network, Cold calling, teamwork and communication. 2020 Top team (CB Union Centre office), Top 10 in sales in Cincinnati (Coldwell Banker)

Title Closer & Marketing Rep, Priority National Title, Liberty Twp, OH — 2021-2022

1st Closer (Head Closer). Job Duties included, Closing Buyers and Sellers on Purchases and Refinances, Training New closers, Preparing documents for closing, Realtor, Loan officer, Loan closer and funder followup and relations, Floater (helped other positions in the company to get a bigger picture overall company. Departments inc. Post closing, Funding, Recording), driving 500+ Miles a week. 1,000+ Closing Experience, 2021 Runner-up Rookie of the year.

EDUCATION

Bowling Green State University - Biology, 2016-2017

University of Cincinnati - Buisness, 2017-2019

Hondros College of Buisness - 2020

Ohio State University - Coding Bootcamp - 2022

SKILLS & CERTIFICATIONS

Ohio Real Estate License

Ohio Notary

Kentucky Notary

REFRENCES

Amber Lynn Withrow - Assistant General Manager, Priority National Title

- Phone: (513) 827-7164

Dollie Martin - Lead Marketer, Priority National Title

- Phone: (513) 623-0632

Lisa Morales - Team Morales, Coldwell Banker Realty

- Phone: (513) 218-0687

Rich Morales - Team Morales, Coldwell Banker Realty

- Phone: (513) 218-0633

Scott Coleman - Firehouse Subs

- Phone (937) 620-6670